<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>The Scellor Race (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.TheScellorRace</packageId>
  <author>Mako Ray</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/TheScellorRace</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies>
    <li>
      <packageId>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</packageId>
      <displayName>Humanoid Alien Races</displayName>
      <steamWorkshopUrl>steam://url/CommunityFilePage/839005762</steamWorkshopUrl>
      <downloadUrl>https://github.com/erdelf/AlienRaces/releases/latest</downloadUrl>
    </li>
  </modDependencies>
  <loadAfter>
    <li>erdelf.HumanoidAlienRaces</li>
  </loadAfter>
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/WAEzk68.png[/img]
Update of Mako Rays mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1987895775

- Fixed the CE-patch to be loaded only if CE is loaded
- Added Empire non-enemy patch

[img]https://i.imgur.com/7Gzt3Rg.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://invite.gg/Mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/TheScellorRace][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/NOW7jU1.png[/img]
A very simple mod that adds a new race to the game. Credit to Jukashi for creating the Scellor. (also to my friends avery and kyle for helping me code and playtest thank u)

[h1]Features[/h1]
Not a whole lot, I mostly made this because I just wanted to have them in my colony.
-Somewhat broader comfy temperature range
-More likely to be pretty, psychically sensitive, and gay (because bisexuality isn't a default trait)
-Orel (head noodle) and tail body parts
-A whole lot of rainbow hair
-A custom faction which is pretty much identical to the civil outlander union human faction because I didn't feel like thinking about what to change
-Some custom alien names of which only 90% were generated using https://www.fantasynamegenerators.com/alien-names.php
-A patch for Combat Extended
-No noses

[h2]Things that should be features but I probably won't ever get around to adding them[/h2]
-Sub-races divided up into their 6 castes, seen here: https://www.furaffinity.net/view/9884959/
-Really anything to significantly distinguish them from standard humans other than being green

[img]https://i.imgur.com/Rs6T6cr.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[/list]
</description>
</ModMetaData>

